(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
常闇トワ 6周年記念 ROCK Festa!!!
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary ROCK Festa!!!
ヘイ！
Hey!
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary LIVE
Artist 常闇トワ
Artist: Tokoyami Towa
Guest 鷹嶺ルイ
Guest: Takane Lui
Guest 輪堂千速
Guest: Rindo Chihaya
Guest IRyS
Guest 音乃瀬奏
Guest: Otonose Kanade
Guest AZKi
Guest 夏色まつり
Guest: Natsuiro Matsuri
Guest 森カリオペ
Guest: Mori Calliope
Guest 猫汰つな
Guest: Nekota Tsuna
BE ALL LIE
作詞・作曲：古閑翔平(YOURNESS)
Lyrics/Composition: Shohei Koga (YOURNESS)
ああ　呆れだすそばに
Ah, as I begin to get fed up by my side
差し替えられた　幻想にかかった
With these substituted, fixed ideas
固定概念と
That have fallen into a fantasy
鼻についた答えじゃ
With an answer that reeks
見透かされてしまうな
I'll be seen right through
この道は渡りきっても
Even if I finish crossing this path
まだ近いと思っている
I still think it's close
履き替えた大人になってから
After becoming an adult who changed shoes
縮みきった歩幅と感情
My stride and emotions have shrunk
削れだしてからだに対して
As my body starts to scrape away
気付けと歌っている
I'm singing to realize it
はみだした心じゃ
If I can't stay
いられないのならさ
With an overflowing heart
染みついたこの青さを
It's okay to separate
切り離してしまっていい
This ingrained blueness
ずっと　語りかけてた日々を
All those days I kept talking to
嘆くように
As if grieving
深い闇に飲み込まれないよって
Saying 'don't be swallowed by the deep darkness'
決まりきった現実に　答えなんてない
In this fixed reality, there are no answers
逃げ出してしまった
Wearing the words
言葉を羽織って
That I ran away from
溶け出した心を
Hiding my melting heart
胸に隠している
In my chest
冷え切ってしまった
As if to deceive
体を騙すように
My chilled body
描きかけた
I'm tracing
いつかの枯れた夢を
A withered dream from long ago
なぞっている
That I once started to draw
ああ　暴れだす言葉に
Ah, with words that start to run wild
差し替えられた　幻想にかかった
With these substituted, fixed ideas
固定概念と
That have fallen into a fantasy
戸惑ったりそうじゃ
If I stay hesitant
見透かされてしまうな
I'll be seen right through
この道は渡りきっても
Even if I finish crossing this path
また誓いだ続いていく
I'll keep thinking of it as a vow
履き違えた大人になってから
After becoming an adult who misunderstood
浮かびだした思いの階層
Layers of thoughts began to surface
ずっと見えなくなった
I'm looking for the footprints
足跡探している
That I've lost sight of
はみだした心じゃ
If I can't stay
いられないのならさ
With an overflowing heart
染み切ったこの青さを
It's okay to expose
さらけだしてしまっていい
This completely ingrained blueness
ずっと　語りかけてた日々を
All those days I kept talking to
隠すように
As if hiding them
深い闇に飲み込まれないよって
Saying 'don't be swallowed by the deep darkness'
決まりきった現実に　答えなんていらない
In this fixed reality, I don't need an answer
逃げ出してしまった
Wearing the words
言葉を羽織って
That I ran away from
溶け出した心を
Hiding my melting heart
胸に隠している
In my chest
冷え切ってしまった
As if to deceive
体を騙すように
My chilled body
描きかけた
I'm tracing
いつかの枯れた夢を
A withered dream from long ago
なぞって
That I once started to draw
ああ　錆びついている
Ah, it's rusting
今をただ
Just standing
不安定に立つ
Unsteadily in the now
裏返る森に
By the days that were defiled
汚されてしまったあの日達に
By the turning forest
抗っては辿ってたって
Even though I had let go
手放してしまったのに
Saying I was struggling and tracing it
逃げ出してしまった
Wearing the words
言葉を羽織って
That I ran away from
溶け出した心を
Hiding my melting heart
胸に隠している
In my chest
冷え切ってしまった
As if to deceive
体を騙すように
My chilled body
描きかけた
I'm tracing
いつかの枯れた夢を
A withered dream from long ago
なぞっている
That I once started to draw
Can you hear me when I cry this desperation?
Nothing comes along with my expectation.
How much prayer echo feeling...
...breathe in...
...I got in this desperation.
アダルトスーツ
Adult Suits
作詞:Taka 作曲:Toru / Taka
Lyrics: Taka  Composition: Toru / Taka
アダルトな着ぐるみ着てる僕
Me, wearing an adult costume
心はいつも 不安定天秤さ
My heart is always an unstable scale
まさかの発言で凍りつく
Frozen by an unexpected remark
色めき隠れ 彷徨う僕
Hiding my colors and wandering
今日今この瞬間にハッとする
Suddenly struck by this moment today
言葉がいつも後ろ髪引く
Words always pull me back
全部ダメダメ なんて事じゃもう 放っておいて
If everything is bad, just leave me alone
端からなかった事にしよう
Let's act like it never happened from the start
それじゃダメダメ 悪い癖だね もう知らない
That's no good. It's a bad habit. I don't care anymore
どうせ期待されているなら
If I'm being expected of anyway
キミキミでいこう
Let's go as you are
何もかもが暗く黒く見える
Everything looks dark and black
色眼鏡付きのアダルトなバッタもんスーツ
An adult knock-off suit with tinted glasses
必殺技かける 0 で全部 消し去ろうか
Should I use my special move and erase it all to zero?
強気な僕
Me, being assertive
だけど実際は やっぱできやしないの
But in reality, I still can't do it
身軽さを奪われ動けない
Stripped of my agility, I can't move
それでも愛言葉 バランスとれてるんだよ
But even so, our code word keeps us in balance
君は耳元でそれを言う
You whisper it in my ear
それにしちゃ少し あんまりじゃない？ ってか不公平じゃない？
Isn't that a bit much? Or rather, isn't it unfair?
どうせガチ目なんてないし
It's not like there's any seriousness anyway
食い気味でいこう
Let's jump right in
I feel this moment. No one can take it.
何万回だって 伝わらなきゃ意味ないないない
No matter how many times, it's meaningless if it doesn't get across
今日今この瞬間が大事なの
Today, this moment is what matters
奪う権利は あなたに手はない
You have no right to take it away
全部ダメダメ 何がダメダメ なんでしょう
Everything is bad? What is so bad about it?
納得いくまで話して
Talk to me until I'm satisfied
どうせ屁理屈 並べるんならバカみたい
If you're just going to make excuses, it's idiotic
とどめを刺す気でいるなら
If you're planning to deliver the final blow
今がチャンスだぞ
Now is your chance
はーい！ということで！
Hi! So!
こんやっぴー！ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様でーす！
Konyappi! It's Hololive 4th Gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
はい！ということで、なんと本日6周年を迎えました！
Yes! So, believe it or not, today I've reached my 6th anniversary!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ろっ、ろく！
Si-six!
悪魔の数字「6」！
The devil's number '6'!
ということで、今年はトワちゃんの年ということでいいでしょうか？
So, can we say this year is Towa-chan's year?
ま、よくないか。
Well, maybe not.
いいか！
It's fine!
ま、人によってはトワちゃんの、ね、あの年にしたっていいということで。
Well, for some people, it's fine to make it Towa-chan's year.
はい、よろしくお願いしまーす！
Yes, please lend me your support!
さてさて、続いては…
Now then, next up...
常闇トワ6周年記念ライブ、でよろしくお願いします！
Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary Live, please enjoy!
目指せトレンド入り！
Aiming for trending!
えー、そしてね、この後はいろんな告知もありますので、
And then, there will be various announcements later,
最後まで見ていってくれればなと思います！
so I hope you watch until the end!
はい。えー、で今日なんですけれども、
Yes. And about today,
1月3日となっておりまして、
it's January 3rd,
世の中はお休みの日ということで、わたくしもお休みの日ということで、
and since it's a holiday for the world, and a holiday for me too,
本日のこのライブは全編収録となっております。
today's live is fully pre-recorded.
よろしくお願いいたします。
Thank you for your understanding.
そして、この後はなんとゲストパート！
And then, next is the guest part!
いっぱい、いろんなゲストが出てくれるので、
Many different guests will appear,
楽しんで見ていってくれればなと思います！
so I hope you enjoy watching!
では、
Well then,
ゲストパート、どうぞ！
guest part, here we go!
絆ノ奇跡
作詞・作曲：Jean-Ken Johnny
Kizuna no Kiseki
Lyrics & Composition: Jean-Ken Johnny
闇夜を駆け抜けて どこへ向かう
Rushing through the dark night, where are we headed?
月明かりだけがただ一筋の道標
Only the moonlight is a single signpost
痛みも悲しみも拭いきれず
Unable to wipe away the pain and sadness
されどこの胸の炎は消させない
Yet I won't let the fire in this chest go out
誰がために僕たちは この思いを貫いて
For whom do we carry out these feelings?
闇を裂き陽の下で 光差す日まで
Tearing through the darkness under the sun, until the day light shines
解き放たれた心に宿した火よ
The fire harbored in the unleashed heart
舞い上げもっと今 夜明けの向こう側へ
Fly up higher now, towards the other side of dawn
似ているこの世界 もう一度愛せるまで
This similar world, until we can love it once more
命、果てたとも 繋いでゆくよ
Even if life ends, we will keep connecting
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
The miracle born from the ties woven together
喜怒哀楽 夢揺らめいてる現世
Joy, anger, grief, and pleasure... the shimmering dreams of this world
互いの正義をまた繰り返し振りかざす
Brandishing our respective justices over and over again
誰がために繋ぐ命
For whose sake do we connect our lives?
交わり縺れる運命
The intertwined and tangled destinies
蛇の道 数多の罪 全てなぎ払え
The path of the serpent, many sins... sweep them all away
解き放て今 僕らが起こした火を
Unleash now, the fire we have started
舞い上げ走れば 明日が変わるはず
If we fly up and run, tomorrow should change
君といるこの世界 二度と離さずに
In this world where I am with you, I'll never let go again
君とともにゆく 瞼を閉じても
Going along with you, even if I close my eyes
思い出すあの日を 打ちのめされても
I'll remember that day, even if I'm defeated
焦がれた未来を
The future I yearned for
いつの日か君に 捧げてみせよう
I'll show you that I'll dedicate it to you someday
解き放たれた心に宿した火よ
The fire harbored in the unleashed heart
舞い上げもっと今 夜明けの向こうへ
Fly up higher now, towards the other side of dawn
解き放て今 僕らが起こした火を
Unleash now, the fire we have started
舞い上げ走れば 明日が変わるはず
If we fly up and run, tomorrow should change
君といたこの世界 もう一度愛せるまで
This world where I was with you, until we can love it once more
命、果てたとも 繋げてゆくよ
Even if life ends, we will keep connecting
絆が紡いで 生まれた奇跡を
The miracle born from the ties woven together
ブルーアンバー
作詞・作曲：清水依与吏
Blue Amber
Lyrics & Composition: Motohiro Shimizu
抱きしめられた記憶から流れ出た赤い雫
A red drop flowed from the memory of being held
他人様に見せるもんじゃないの
It's not something to show to others
伝えられなかった言霊がもう一人の私になって
The unspoken words became another version of me
体の内側で何かを叫んでる
And they're screaming something deep inside
欲しかったのに
Even though I wanted it
悔しかったのに
Even though I was frustrated
駄目だよ 全部隠しておくの
It's no good, I have to hide it all
ごめんね
I'm sorry
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
Saying that being sad is enough for one person
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
Saying I don't want to become any uglier than this
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Inside of me, without being found by anyone
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
You've been crying until you turned this color
綺麗だよ
It's beautiful
私そびれた心から流れ出た青い雫
A blue drop flowed from a heart that missed out
他人様に浴びせるもんじゃないの
It's not something to shower others with
全部遠くへ飲み込んで遠くの海原底に沈んで
Swallow it all deep down and sink it to the sea floor
そのまま宝石にでもなれるのを待つの
And wait for it to eventually become a gemstone
本当は嘘で飾って
Decorating the truth with lies
毒みたいなくらしで慰めて
Consoling myself in a life like poison
誰かの悲劇で自分の悲劇を癒して
Healing my own tragedy with someone else's
恋しさに溺れた瞬間のままで
Remaining at the moment I drowned in longing
息も出来ずただ愛してるの
I love you, simply unable to even breathe
悲しいのは一人で十分だからと
Saying that being sad is enough for one person
これ以上醜くなりたくないのと
Saying I don't want to become any uglier than this
私の中で誰にも見つけられずに
Inside of me, without being found by anyone
こんな色になるまで泣いていたんだね
You've been crying until you turned this color
綺麗だよ
It's beautiful
ごめんね
I'm sorry
ねえ
Hey
綺麗だよ
It's beautiful
蝶々結び
作詞・作曲：野田洋次郎
Chocho Musubi
Lyrics & Composition: Yojiro Noda
片っぽで丸を作って しっかり持ってて
Make a loop with one end, and hold it tight
もう片っぽでその丸の後ろを ぐるっと回って
With the other end, wrap it around the back of that loop
間にできたポッケに入って 出てくるの待ってて
Go into the pocket made in between, and wait for it
出てきたところを迎えにきて せーので引っぱって
Come to meet it when it emerges, and pull together
初めは何とも情けない形だとしても
Even if at first it's a somewhat pathetic shape
同じだけ力を込めて
Put in equal amounts of strength
羽は大きく 結び目は固く なるようにきつく
So the wings are large and the knot is firm
結んでいてほしいの
I want you to keep it tied
出会いはここに
The encounter is here
思い出は遠くに
The memories are far away
置いておいてほしい ほしいの
I want you to leave them be, I want you to
片っぽでも引っ張っちゃえば
If you pull just one side...
ほどけちゃうけど
...it'll come undone.
作ったもの壊すのは
But breaking what was made...
はるかに簡単だけど
...is far easier.
だけどほどくときも そうちゃんと
But when undoing it, also properly...
同じようにね
...the same way, right?
わかってるよ でもできたらね
I know, but if possible...
せーので引っ張って
...pull together on 'one, two'.
ほどきやしないようにと願って
Wishing it won't come undone...
力込めては
...putting strength into it.
広げすぎた羽に
Upon wings spread too wide...
戸惑う
...I'm perplexed.
羽は大きく 結び目は固く
Make the wings large, the knot tight.
なるようにきつく
To make it stay that way...
結んでいてほしいの
...I want you to tie it firmly.
夢はここに
Dreams are here.
思い出は遠くに
Memories are far away.
日付けもそこにある
It's better if even the date...
くらいがいい
...is just about there.
黙って引っ張ったりしないでよ
Don't just pull it silently.
不格好な蝶にしないでよ
Don't turn it into an ugly butterfly.
結んだつもりがほどけていたり
What I thought was tied might come undone...
緩めたつもりが締めていたり
...and what I thought was loosened might be tightened.
この青くて広い世界に
In this blue and vast world...
無数に散らばった中から
...from among the countless scattered things...
別々に二人選んだ糸を
...we each chose a separate thread...
お互い手繰り寄せ合ったんだ
...and pulled them together.
結ばれたんじゃなく結んだんだ
We weren't tied together; we tied it ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
The two of us pulled together on 'one, two'.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように
So it doesn't become too big or too small...
力を込めたんだ
...we put our strength into it.
この青くて広い世界に
In this blue and vast world...
無数に散らばった中から
...from among the countless scattered things...
別々に二人選んだ糸を
...we each chose a separate thread...
お互い手繰り寄せ合ったんだ
...and pulled them together.
結ばれたんじゃなく結んだんだ
We weren't tied together; we tied it ourselves.
二人でせーので引っ張ったんだ
The two of us pulled together on 'one, two'.
大きくも小さくもなりすぎないように
So it doesn't become too big or too small...
力を込めたんだ
...we put our strength into it.
花になって
Become a Flower
陰にそっと隠れようがいいんじゃない
Isn't it fine to hide quietly in the shadows?
蕾のような花だってあんじゃない
Aren't there flowers like buds too?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない
Isn't it better to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず華麗に咲いてる
Blooming magnificently without being disturbed.
甘い苦いにハマんない
I won't get hooked on sweet or bitter.
その判断が下んない
That judgment won't be made.
気に病んで下向かないでいて
Don't worry and look down.
愛に慣れちゃいない
I'm not used to love.
無駄に飾んない
I won't decorate pointlessly.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
A vase made pretty...
肥やしも何もいらない
...doesn't need fertilizer or anything.
その姿が美しい
That form is beautiful.
花になって
Become a flower.
ほらニヒルに笑って
Look, smile nihilistically.
その顔に
At that face...
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
...I'm shivering and can't look away.
味見して
Take a taste.
君の毒は私の薬って
Your poison is my medicine...
包んであげるから
...so I'll wrap you up.
…笑って
...and laugh.
会いたい 会いたい
I want to see you, I want to see you.
その笑顔に
That smile of yours...
会いたい 会いたい
I want to see you, I want to see you.
と言えば笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll laugh if I say that.
虜にさせるくらいは
Just enough to make you a captive...
いいんじゃない
...should be fine, right?
欲を言えばこの手で
If I'm being greedy, I want to make you...
咲かせて見せたい
...bloom with these hands.
病のように
Like an illness...
心は喰らう花
...the heart is a flower that consumes.
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want to let it wither.
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach...
水をあげ続けるから
...I'll keep giving it water.
いい加減に気付いて
Please realize it already,
君は素敵って
that you are wonderful.
自惚れてもっとお大事に
Be more vain and take better care of yourself.
無自覚なまま
While remaining unaware...
愛を蓄えて
...store up love.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Even the cleaned vase...
肥やしも何もいらない
...needs no fertilizer or anything else.
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom with pride just as you are.
花になって
Become a flower.
ほら、淫らに笑ってその顔に
Look, laugh wantonly with that face.
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
I'm shivering and can't take my eyes off you.
味見して
Have a taste,
君の毒は私の薬って
your poison is my medicine.
包んであげるから
Because I'll wrap you up.
楽にして
Take it easy,
君の闇は私の光って
your darkness is my light.
愛してあげるから
Because I'll love you.
笑って
Laugh.
多分私じゃなくていいぜ
Probably, it doesn't have to be me.
余裕のない二人だったし
We were a pair with no room to breathe.
気付けば喧嘩ばかりしてさ
Before we knew it, all we did was fight.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
ずっと話そうと思ってた
I'd been thinking about talking to you.
きっと私たち合わないね
I'm sure we're just not right for each other.
二人きりしかいない部屋でさ
In a room with just the two of us...
あなたばかり話していたよね
...you were the only one talking, weren't you?
もし いつか
If, someday,
どこかで会えたら
we meet somewhere...
今日のことを
...about today,
笑ってくれるかな
...I wonder if you'll laugh.
理由もちゃんと
The reason too,
話せないけれど
I can't quite explain it, but...
あなたが眠った後に
...after you fell asleep,
泣くのは嫌だ
...I hate crying.
声も
Your voice,
顔も
your face,
不器用なとこも
even your clumsy parts...
全部
all of it,
嫌いじゃないの
I don't hate them.
ドライフラワーみたい
Like dried flowers,
君との日々も
the days with you...
きっと きっと きっと きっと
...surely, surely, surely, surely...
色褪せる
...will fade away.
多分君じゃなくてよかった
Probably, I'm glad it wasn't you.
もう泣かされることもないし
I won't be made to cry anymore,
「私ばかり」なんて言葉も
and words like "it's always me"...
なくなった
...have disappeared.
あんなに悲しい別れでも
Even with such a sad parting,
時間が経てば忘れてく
as time passes, I start to forget.
新しい人と並ぶ君は
Standing beside someone new,
ちゃんと上手くやれているのかな
I wonder if you're doing well.
もう顔も
Already, your face,
見たくないからさ
I don't want to see it anymore.
変に連絡
Weirdly contacting me...
してこないでほしい
...is something I hope you don't do.
都合がいいのは
Being convenient...
変わってないんだね
...hasn't changed, has it?
でも無視できずにまた
But unable to ignore it again,
少し返事
I give a short reply.
声も
Your voice,
顔も
your face,
不器用なとこも
even your clumsy parts...
多分
Probably,
今も
even now,
嫌いじゃないの
I don't hate them.
ドライフラワーみたいだ
Like a dry flower
時間が経てばきっと きっと きっと きっと
As time goes by, surely, surely, surely, surely
色あせる
The colors will fade
月明かりに魔物が揺れる きっと私もどうかしている
A monster sways in the moonlight, I must be going crazy too
暗闇に色彩が浮かぶ
Colors float in the darkness
赤、黄、青色が胸の奥 ずっとあなたの名前を呼ぶ
Red, yellow, blue deep in my chest, always calling your name
好きという気持ち また薫る
The feeling of love scents the air again
声も 顔も 不器用なとこも
Your voice, your face, even your clumsiness
全部 全部 大嫌いだよ
I hate them all, all of them
まだ枯れない花を 君に添えてさ
Placing a flower that hasn't withered yet by your side
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと
Forever, forever, forever, forever
抱えてよ
Keep holding onto it
二人三脚 feat. 猫汰つな / 作詞：徳田光希 作曲・編曲：三好啓太 / 徳田光希
Ninin Sankyaku feat. Nekose Tsuna / Lyrics: Mitsuki Tokuda / Composition/Arrangement: Keita Miyoshi / Mitsuki Tokuda
「大丈夫」と
Saying "I'm okay"
また嘘をついた
I told another lie
無理してるの
You're overextending yourself
声でわかるよ バレてるんだよ
I can tell by your voice, I've seen through you
二人三脚
Ninin Sankyaku
ダメなとこも 性格だって違うあなた
You, with different flaws and personality from me
だけど似てる どこか痛いとこ合って
But we're similar, our sore spots align somehow
共鳴 すぐにしたんだ
We resonated instantly
共鳴
Resonance
惹かれ合った私たち
Drawn to each other
惹かれ合っ
不思議なこの絆
This mysterious bond
なんだか眠れなくて
Makes it hard to sleep somehow
月夜語り明かそう 明日まで
Let's talk under the moon until tomorrow
私が頑張れる理由 そう 一人じゃないから
The reason I can keep going is because I'm not alone
そう 一人じゃないから
That's right, because I'm not alone
あなたが笑えば 私もつられる
When you laugh, I can't help but laugh too
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Our hearts side-by-side are in a chain reaction
時には歩幅が ズレてしまうけど
Sometimes our strides might get out of sync
時には歩幅が
Sometimes our strides
二人 呼吸合わせ
Let's synchronize our breathing
二人
Two people
未来へと進んで行こう
And move toward the future together
どれくらいの 順位かなんて周りと比べて
Comparing where we stand in the rankings with those around us
果てしない トラック先 追いつけるの？
Can we catch up on the endless track ahead?
なんて弱気な日も 激励し続けてくれた
On those faint-hearted days, you kept encouraging me
あなたにいつも感謝 転んでも立ち上がる
I'm always grateful to you; I'll get back up even if I fall
あなたにいつも感謝
I'm always grateful to you
いつだって 夢を叶えたいんだ 必ず
I always want to make my dreams come true, without fail
こんなにね 打ち込めるのは そう 仲間がいるから
The reason I can devote myself so much is because I have a companion
仲間がいるから
Because I have a companion
あなたの悩みは 私が寄り添う
I'll stay by your side through your worries
私が寄り添う
I'll stay by your side
心が疲れたなら 休憩しよう
If your heart is tired, let's take a break
心が疲れれたなら 休憩しよ
遠慮はしないで そんな仲じゃない 二人
Don't hesitate; we're not that kind of strangers
二人
Two people
肩を組んで ほら 何度でも乗り越え
Putting our arms around each other, see, we can overcome anything time and again
手を組んで ほら 何度でも乗り越えるよ
Hand in hand, see, we'll overcome anything again and again
世界中が敵になっても
Even if the whole world becomes our enemy
変わらずあなたの味方
I'll always be on your side
右と左
Right and left
友達の証だよって
As a symbol of our friendship
強く固くきつく 縛ったリボン
A ribbon tied strong, firm, and tight
笑い合う ドラマも
The dramas we laughed through together
滲んでる 空も
The hazy sky too
掴み取れる 栄光も
And the glory we can seize
一緒に見たい
I want to see them all with you
あなたが 笑えば
If you smile
私も 強くなれる
I can become stronger too
隣り合わせの心 連鎖してるよ
Side-by-side hearts, linking together
いずれそれぞれの道を歩いても
Even if we eventually walk separate paths
共に支え合おうさ
Let's support each other
さあ未来へと進んで行こう
Come, let's move forward into the future
どこにいても 二人三脚
Wherever we are, in a three-legged race
with you...
うぉー！つなだー！つなだー！
Whoa! It's Tsuna! It's Tsuna!
2度目だけど... つなだー！
It's the second time, but... It's Tsuna!
もう忘れてたから... イエーイ！
I already forgot, so... Yay!
6周年！6！
6th Anniversary! 6!
あ、そっちで？
Oh, with that one?
こっちじゃないの？
Not this one?
あ、こう？
Ah, like this?
韓国はこうだよ
In Korea, it's like this.
あー！勉強になりました、ありがとうございます
Ah! I learned something new, thank you.
6がこうなんですね、おめでとう！
So 6 is like this. Congratulations!
ありがとー！嬉しいー！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
そうなんですよ、実はこの前、つなのね...
That's right, actually just recently, for Tsuna's...
記念ライブ...
Anniversary live...
誕生日ね！
Birthday, right!
そう、誕生日記念のライブに出させていただいたので...
Yes, I was allowed to appear in your birthday anniversary live...
今回は...
So this time...
え、なんかさ、初めてなんだよね
Um, it's like, it's the first time, right?
そう、ホロライブのステージに来ましたー！
Yes, I've come to the Hololive stage!
あはは、めちゃくちゃ喜んでる、イエーイ！
Ahaha, you're so happy. Yay!
イエーイ！ありがとう、わざわざ来てくれて。そうなんだよね
Yay! Thank you for coming all this way. That's right.
いっぱい吸ってきます
I'll breathe it all in.
初めて、そう、ホロライブのスタジオで3Dでコラボしました、ありがとうー！
Our first time, yes, collaborating in 3D in the Hololive studio. Thank you!
こちらこそありがとう！
Thank you as well!
そして、なんと、2年ぶりですよ！
And, surprisingly, it's been two years!
そうなんだよね
That's right.
この二人三脚という曲をやらせていただいたんですけど...
We performed this song called "Ninin San-kyaku"...
トワのファーストソロライブの時に...
At the time of Towa's first solo live...
初めてやって...
We did it for the first time...
覚えてた？振り
Did you remember? The choreography.
いや、もう、完全に忘れてた！
No, well, I completely forgot!
でも分かる、色んなのをやってくと、こう、忘れちゃうから。しかも2年ぶりだし
But I get it. If you do various things, you tend to forget. Plus it's been two years.
忘れちゃったけど、でも前はさ、シークレットゲストだったじゃん
I forgot, but before, you were a secret guest, right?
で、初めてなんか、こう、サムネで私がいる！
And for the first time, like, I'm in the thumbnail!
そう！「いる！」ってなって
Yes! I was like, "I'm here!"
嬉しい！でも本当にね、あの曲、あそこで終わりじゃなくて、こうやってまた出来たのがすごく嬉しいので...
I'm happy! But really, that song, it didn't end there, and I'm so happy we could do it again like this...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ということでね、なんかソロライブの時にコラボしたあと、こうやって3Dでコラボすることなかったから...
So, after collaborating during the solo live, we didn't have a chance to collaborate in 3D like this...
今日は、皆さんで無料で今お届けしてるので！
Today, we are bringing it to everyone for free right now!
無料です！
It's free!
じゃあ写真タイムするか！え、する！？改めて...
Then, shall we have a photo time? Eh, we are!? Once again...
どんなポーズがいいですか？
What kind of pose would be good?
指動かして...
Move your fingers...
だっさ、動き。何今のこれ、何？
That's so lame, that movement. What was that just now? What?
陰キャピース
Inkyac peace.
可愛い、可愛くピースやってみてよ
Cute, try doing a cute peace sign.
え、何が可愛いの？
Eh, what's cute?
これ古いです、古いって言われない？大丈夫？
This is old. Won't people say it's old? Is it okay?
今の流行りは？
What's the trend now?
今の流行り何？
What's the current trend?
これ、これ、これ？
This, this, this?
え、指が、ちゅあちゅあしてる
Eh, the fingers are... 'chua chua'-ing?
あ、これ！私もやりたいです！
Ah, this! I want to do it too!
おおー！すごーい！
Ohh! Amazing!
だっさ！
Lame!
喜びのダンス
Dance of joy.
あ、出た。ビジュき、アイドル
Ah, there it is. Visual... idol.
アイドルね
Idol, right.
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
いっぱい撮ってねー！
Take lots of photos!
ありがとー！え、どう？
Thank you! Eh, how's this?
なんだよ、おい
What is this, hey.
え、ハート作るからさ... ピー... あの、グーして
Eh, I'll make a heart, so... Pe... Um, make a fist.
トワがグーの方？
Towa is the fist side?
グーして
Make a fist.
あー！ありがとうございます！
Ah! Thank you so much!
サンガ、サンガ、嬉しい。可愛い！ステージ戻ろ！
Thanks, thanks, I'm happy. Cute! Let's go back to the stage!
可愛い / かっこいい
So cute! / So cool!
こよちゃんも可愛いじゃないですか
Koyochu-chan, you're cute too, aren't you?
えー、嬉しいです！
Oh, I'm so happy!
なんかすごい...はだけちゃってごめんなさいね
It's like... sorry for being a bit exposed like this.
トワちゃんにはないものを持ってるような気がして、すごい
I feel like I have things you don't, Towa-chan. It's amazing.
やめてください
Please stop.
でも別に何がとか言ってないですけども
But I didn't say what exactly I have!
あ、そうですか？あ、そうそうですね
Oh, really? Ah, right, right.
ということでね、今日は本当に来てくれてありがとうございました
Anyway, thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそ！ありがとう！
Me too! Thank you!
またね、コラボもしよう！
Let's collab again sometime!
しよう！遊ぼう！
Let's! Let's play!
遊ぼう！
Let's play!
ということで、以上、常闇トワでしたー！
So, that's all from Tokoyami Towa!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
頑張って！ / ありがとう！
Good luck! / Thank you!
胸を剥ぐれて
Stripped of my heart
夢をくわえた
Clutching a dream in my teeth
それが最後に
I felt like that
なる気がしたんだ
Would be the last time
獣は砂を
The beast scattered
一握り撒いた
A handful of sand
それが最後に
I felt like that
なる気がしたんだ
Would be the last time
不確かな夢叶えるのさ
I'll make that uncertain dream come true
約束の夜に
On the night of the promise
微かな風に願うのさ
I'll wish upon the faint wind
静寂の朝に
In the silence of the morning
遠い星の証明は
The proof of a distant star
その腕に約束の飾り
Is the ornament of promise on that arm
まだ旅路の最中さ
I'm still in the middle of the journey
幻惑の空に
In the dazzling sky
霞んで消えた
Faded into the haze
轍の先へ
Beyond the tracks
それが最後に
I felt like that
なる気がしたんだ
Would be the last time
古い夢を
If I re-spin
紡ぎ直せば
The old dream
それが最後に
I felt like that
なる気がしたんだ
Would be the last time
熱砂を蹴り抗うのさ
Kicking the hot sand, I'll resist
約束の前に
Before the promise
命綱はないのさ
There's no safety rope
サーカスの夜に
On the night of the circus
まだ旅路の最中さ
I'm still in the middle of the journey
あの場所に加速するさらに
Accelerating even more toward that place
雨上がりのシャンデリア
A chandelier after the rain
幻惑の空に
In the dazzling sky
SWISH THE CHUCK YO!
Pass gon' a penetrate a best be far
Get deeper buzz of beat
Burst on a penetrate a best be far
What a buzz of beat
Just what a buzz of beat
Pass gon' a penetrate a best be far
Get deeper buzz of beat
What a buzz of beat
Just what a buzz of beat
Pass gon' a penetrate a best be far
What a buzz of beat
Just what a buzz of beat
脳内更地に X-PASS
An X-PASS in the brain's wasteland
食わずのイハビ
Without ever tasting it
スイちゃーんよー！
Suisei-chan here!
永遠の意味を知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity
答えを示せる時が来た
The time has come to show the answer
無限に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinitely continuing spiral
問いの裏に聞こえた理由は
The reason I heard behind the question
儚い未来手繰った弱さ
Was the fragility of reaching for a fleeting future
それを強さとはき違えている
I've mistaken that for strength
憎い　醜い
Hateful, ugly
月を隠すほどの
Enough to hide the moon
黒く　淀む　心
Black, stagnant, heart
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here
揺らいでる　揺らいでる
Swaying, swaying
花のように萎（しぼ）む　意思を繋ぐ
Connecting the will that withers like a flower
奪っていく　奪っていく
Taking away, taking away
嵐のように心　疼く
Like a storm, my heart aches
永遠の意味を知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity
答えを示せる時が来た
The time has come to show the answer
無限に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinitely continuing spiral
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
生まれ落ちた運命（さだめ）を飲んで
Drinking the fate I was born into
背負った傷の名前を覚えた
I remembered the names of the scars I carried
溢れるほど　心燃やす感情
Emotions that burn my heart to overflowing
憎い　醜い
Hateful, ugly
世界を分かつほどの
Enough to divide the world
怒り　燃やす　心
Anger, burning heart
君さえいなければ
If only you weren't here
揺らいでる　揺らいでる
Swaying, swaying
花のように萎（しぼ）む　意思を繋ぐ
Connecting the will that withers like a flower
奪っていく　奪っていく
Taking away, taking away
嵐のように心　疼く
Like a storm, my heart aches
永遠の意味を知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity
答えを示せる時が来た
The time has come to show the answer
無限に続く螺旋の先へ
To the end of the infinitely continuing spiral
地獄耳　傾け仕舞いよ
Lend your sharp ears, it's the end
この身に宿れば万事出仕舞いよ
If it dwells in this body, it's all over
逃げを他者に託した弱き人
A weak person who entrusts their escape to others
命の輝きは幾千層に
The radiance of life is in thousands of layers
祈りの瞬きが照らすように
Like the twinkling of prayers shining
夜を宿し
Harbor the night
回答を叩きつけろ
And strike back with the answer
枯らしていく　枯らしていく
Wither away, wither away
夢幻の夜に花を咲く
Flowers bloom in the phantom night
繋いでいく　繋いでいく
Connecting, connecting
嵐に種を撒いていく
Sowing seeds in the storm
揺らいでる　揺らいでる
Swaying, swaying
花のように萎（しぼ）む　意思を繋ぐ
Connecting the will that withers like a flower
奪っていく　奪っていく
Taking away, taking away
嵐のように心　疼く
Like a storm, my heart aches
永遠の意味を知らぬ君に
To you, who knows not the meaning of eternity
答えを示せる時が来た
The time has come to show the answer
無限に続く螺旋の先で
At the end of the infinitely continuing spiral
待つのは誰
Who is waiting?
以上、ゲストパートでした！
That's it for the guest segment!
ゲストパートでしたー！　いぇーい！
That was the guest segment! Yay!
はい。ということで、たくさんのメンバーがね、お祝いしに来てくれました！　やったー！
Yes. So, many members came to celebrate! Hooray!
そして、本日の6周...
And, for today's 6th anni...
記念ライブなんですけれども
This is the anniversary live, but...
ロックフェスみたいなのをちょっとイメージしておりまして
I've been imagining it as something like a rock festival.
ちょっとね、えー、ダンスよりも、
So, well, rather than dancing,
あの、好きに動いてねのフリーの動きを多めにしてみたので
I've tried to include more 'free movement', moving as you please.
えー、それぞれのゲストとトワちゃんのね、えー、個性がでてるパフォーマンスになってるんじゃないかなと思います！
I think it's a performance where the personalities of each guest and myself really shine!
なので、配信とかを見返して「あ、ここ癖出てるな」とか
So I'd be happy if you could rewatch the stream and think, "Oh, there's a quirk of hers,"
思いながらもう一回改めて見ていただけると嬉しいです！
while watching it all over again!
そして、まだこのあとも歌いますから、
And there's more singing to come,
チャンネルはそのままで！
so don't change the channel!
ブイッ
Peace!
で、プチ告知させてもらいます！
Now, let me make a small announcement!
はい。
Yes.
えー、セカンドソロライブで発表いたしました
As announced at my second solo live,
「勇者パーティーを追い出された器用貧乏」という
the MV for "Shirube", the theme song for the anime
アニメの主題歌「シルベ」のMVが
"The Utility Man Who Was Kicked Out of the Hero's Party",
このあと、配信が終わり次第、
will be uploaded to the Towa Channel
トワチャンネルにて上がります！
as soon as this stream ends!
めちゃくちゃ良いMVになったので、ぜひぜひ見てください！
It's a really great MV, so please, please watch it!
見ないと、人生を損したまでとはいかないかもしれないけど、
If you don't watch it, well, maybe it's not a "missing out on life" level loss,
損するかもしれないぐらいです！
but it's pretty close!
はい、気合を入れて作ってもらいました！
Yes, we put a lot of heart into making it!
はい、よろしくお願いします。
Yes, thank you.
そしてアニメはなんと明日から放送開始！
And the anime actually starts airing tomorrow!
楽しみ！ぜひ見てね！
I'm so excited! Please watch it!
そして MVだけではありません。
And it's not just the MV.
ありません。
It's not.
シルベの、なんと！
There's also, believe it or not,
シングルCDが発売決定！
a single CD release decided for "Shirube"!
本日から予約できまーす！
Reservations are open starting today!
なんですけども、こちらの詳細は配信の最後にまとめてお伝えするので、
However, I'll provide more details at the end of the stream,
ここもチャンネルはそのままで。
so don't change the channel.
そしてさらに本日はね、周年記念なのでグッズのお知らせもあります！
And what's more, since today is the anniversary, there's also news about merch!
もちろん！
Of course!
はい、こちらも詳細を後でまたお伝えしますので、
Yes, I'll give you more details on this later as well,
チャンネルはそのままで。
so don't change the channel.
今日のキーワードは「チャンネルはそのままで」。
Today's keyword is "don't change the channel."
えーそしてね、メン限のミニライブも今日はありますので、
And we'll also have a members-only mini-live today,
ぜひメンバーシップに入っていただけたら嬉しくて、
so I'd be happy if you joined the membership,
チャンネルはそのままで。
and don't change the channel.
あはは、どんだけ言うんだよ。
Hahaha, how many times am I gonna say it?
はい、ということでありがとうございました。
Alright, thank you very much.
はい、じゃあ最後に一曲歌ってから告知しようかなと思うので、聞いてください。
Well then, I'll sing one last song before the announcements, so please listen.
最後の一曲、「シルベ」。
The last song, "Shirube."
Warning! Warning! 隣り合わせ
Warning! Warning! Side by side
May God bless you 言葉の綾ね
May God bless you, a figure of speech
Warning! Warning! 彷徨いながら
Warning! Warning! While wandering
I will stay true to myself 'cause of you
「はじめから」みたいに
Like 'from the beginning',
何もない世界に
in a world where there's nothing.
理不尽に囚われる
Captive to absurdity,
黙ってしまうほどの恐怖はない
there's no fear enough to make me fall silent.
使い捨てみたいに
Like something disposable,
手を離したあなたに
to you who let go.
昨日とはまるで違うって わかったところで しょうもない
Even knowing it's completely different from yesterday is pointless.
変わっていく身体と 心の中で響く Voice
My changing body and the Voice echoing in my heart.
間違ってなかったと ただこの空を眺めてる
That I wasn't wrong, I'm just gazing at this sky.
I still 重なってたび 思い出して しまうのに
I still, every time they overlap, even though I end up remembering...
誤魔化して しまうのは 確かにあった 後悔から
The reason I end up hiding it is from a regret that definitely existed.
誓い合わず 折ったはずなんだ さよならすらシルベにしよう
We didn't make a vow, we should've broken it; let's make even 'goodbye' our guide.
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
As if I end up wishing every time I touch the light.
And still I rise!!
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to be stained.
超えられない Border 揺れる思考を Convert
The uncrossable Border, Convert my swaying thoughts.
嘘で染めるような日々じゃ 振り返った時には Heartache
In days like staining with lies, looking back there's only Heartache.
また夜が明ける Wake up 夢の中の Flavor
The dawn breaks again, Wake up, the Flavor in my dreams.
誰もいなくなった道を歩いている
I'm walking a path where everyone has gone.
今の私に 迷いすら重なってくる おとぎ話の正体
To my current self, even doubts overlap; the true nature of fairy tales.
誤魔化しきれなかった 心が纏う熱を
The heat my heart wears, which I couldn't fully hide.
憧れが照らしてる
Yearning is illuminating.
I still 重なってたび 思い出して しまうのに
I still, every time they overlap, even though I end up remembering...
誤魔化して しまうのは 大人になった 後悔から
The reason I end up hiding it is from a regret that grew into adulthood.
月明かりの夜は さよならすらシルベにしよう
On a moonlit night, let's make even our goodbyes a guide.
光を繋ぐたび 浮かぶ星座のように
Like constellations that appear every time we connect the lights.
選んできた道のりを今を
The path I've chosen and where I am now...
いずれ後悔してしまう時が来ても
...even if a time comes when I regret it all.
私はまだ止まらない
I still won't stop.
夜空に浮かぶ月の光を
Taking the moonlight in the night sky...
見上げた空に散らばる星の宝石を
...and the starry jewels scattered in the heavens I look up at.
道標にして 帰る場所
Making them a guide to the place I return to.
I still 重なってたび
I still keep remembering every time...
思い出してしまうのに
...things seem to overlap.
誤魔化してしまうのは
The reason I hide it...
確かにあった後悔から
...is because of the regrets that were certainly there.
誓ったはずなんだ
I should have sworn...
さよならすらシルベにしよう
...to make even our goodbyes a guide.
光に触れるたび 願ってしまうように
So that every time I touch the light, I make a wish.
And still I rise!!
染まっていく必要もない
There's no need to be tainted...
どれも哀を模した true
...it's all a truth modeled after sorrow.
はい！ということで常闇トワ6周年記念ライブを
Yes! And with that, thank you so much for watching
見ていただきましてありがとうございました！
Tokoyami Towa's 6th Anniversary Live!
ノンストップでお届けしてまいりましたがいかがだったでしょうかー？
I delivered it all non-stop, so how did you like it?
たくさんね、タグを使って感想コメントを待っております！
I'm waiting for lots of feedback and comments using the hashtags!
ということで、この後はお知らせをさせていただきたいと思います！
So, after this, I'd like to make some announcements!
まず、1つ目！さっきね、歌った「シルベ」を収録した
First off, number one! It's been decided that
シングルの発売が決定してしまいましたー！
a single containing 'Silhouetter' will be released!
イエーイ！
Yay!
今回のジャケット写真は、Graphite77さんに描き下ろしていただきました！
The jacket illustration for this release was drawn by Graphite77!
3月25日発売で、今回も全国流通での発売となります！
It'll be released on March 25th, and it will be available nationwide!
イエーイ！そしてね、なんとカップリングには
Yay! And surprisingly, the B-side
「Present Day」のライブバージョンが入ります！
will include the live version of 'Present Day'!
Yournessさん繋がりということでね、
Since they're both connected to Yourness,
「Present Day」はソロライブ「常闇トワ 2nd Live」の音源を使用した楽曲が
'Present Day' will feature the audio from my 'Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live' solo concert,
収録されておりますので、楽しみに待っておいてください！
so please look forward to it!
はい！そして今回は、完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種をご用意しております。
Yes! And this time, we have two versions: the Limited Edition and the Regular Edition.
ということで、こちら！ボーン！
So, here they are! Bam!
完全生産限定盤には、オリジナルTシャツが入っております！
The Limited Edition comes with an original T-shirt!
今回の「シルベ」のジャケットイラストを使ったオリジナルTシャツとなっております。
It features the jacket illustration for 'Silhouetter.'
通常盤には、初回プレス限定特典として、ジャケットイラストステッカーが入ってます。
The Regular Edition includes a jacket illustration sticker as a first-press bonus.
ステッカーもね、スマホに入れたり、アケコンやパソコンとかに貼ってもらえたら嬉しいなと思ってます。
I'd be happy if you put it on your phone, arcade controller, or PC.
はい！こちらは本日21時から予約開始なんですが、
Pre-orders start today at 9:00 PM,
なんと、ホロライブ公式ECではこの配信中にCDが買えるようになってるかも！
but you might even be able to buy it on the Hololive Official EC during this stream!
ということで、楽しみに待っててください！チェックしてねー！
So please look forward to it and check it out!
はい！そして2つ目なんですが、
Alright! And for the second announcement,
常闇トワ活動6周年記念ライブグッズ...ライブじゃねーわ、グッズ！
merchandise for Tokoyami Towa's 6th anniversary... not live, just merchandise!
が、発売いたします！
It's going on sale!
イエーイ！今回は数量限定盤もありますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
Yay! There's a limited quantity version too, so please check it out.
ということで、気になる内容は、こちら！ボーン！と。
So, here's what's inside! Bam!
活動6周年記念フルセット、こんな感じになっております。ジャジャーン！
The 6th Anniversary Full Set looks like this. Ta-da!
では、細かく見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a closer look!
まず1つ目はこちら！
First up is this!
「#Towavelしてね！」アクリルジオラマスタンド！
The '#Towavel' Acrylic Diorama Stand!
ということで、イラストは大熊まい先生に書いていただきました。
The illustration was drawn by Ohkuma Mai-sensei.
ちょっとね、大人っぽいトワちゃんと一緒にあの、デート的なの行ってもらえればなと思います。
I'd like you to go on something like a date with this slightly more mature Towa-chan.
いつもね、Towavelね、みんなしてくれててありがとうございます。
Thank you all for always doing '#Towavel' for me.
これね、あの、本体をね、こう取り出して...ま、本体ってトワのことなんだけど、
You can take out the main piece... well, the 'main piece' is me, Towa,
トワを取り出して、一緒にね、写真が撮れるポージングにしてるの。ぜひ一緒にね、Towavelしてポストしてみてね。
and take photos together. Please go '#Towavel-ing' with me and post about it.
はい！では次はこちら！
Alright! Next is this!
トワとお揃い！ジャージ！
A track jacket just like mine!
トワのね、通常衣装の服をイメージしたジャージとなっております。
It's a track jacket designed after my standard outfit.
これね、あの、トワと全く一緒にすると、とんでもない露出度になるので、
If it were exactly like mine, the level of exposure would be crazy,
長めの...着やすい...はい！
so it's longer and easy to wear... yes!
はい、着やすいね、サイズにさせていただいております。
Yes, we've made it in an easy-to-wear size.
よかった。
I'm glad.
ちゃんと裏地もね、ネオンピンクみたいな形のネオンピンク、
形じゃないね、ネオンピンクの色になってますから、
The lining is also neon pink, like a neon pink shape...
not a shape, it's a neon pink color,
本当にトワ様をになっちゃったみたいなジャージになってます。
so it's a jersey that makes you feel like you've really become Towa-sama.
ちょっと大きめのサイズなんで、あの、みんな着やすいのかなと思います。
It's a bit of an oversized fit, so I think it'll be easy for everyone to wear.
はい！ということで、じゃあ最後3つ目。
Alright! Now for the third and final item.
ビビハンドストラップ！
The Bibi Hand Strap!
やっぱね、あの、結構トワのジャージとかは結構ザ・グッズ、
グッズというかさ、キャラグッズみたいな感じするんですけど、
You know, Towa's jerseys and such often feel like...
'THE merch,' or like character goods,
通常使いもね、しやすいような、使い勝手の良いような、
グッズも欲しいなと思いましてハンドストラップを作ってみました。
but I also wanted some goods that are easy to use every day,
so I made this hand strap.
イエーイ！
Yay!
カラーリングもね、すごい落ち着いていて、
トワっぽい色になったんじゃないかなと思うので、ぜひ購入お願いいたしてまーす。
The coloring is also very subdued and turned out quite
'Towa-like,' so please consider buying it.
こちら、スマートフォンの画像は付いておりますが、
スマートフォンは付いてきませんので、よろしくお願いします。
Also, while there's an image of a smartphone here,
the smartphone itself is not included, so please keep that in mind.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
はい！で、こちらのセットをご購入してくださった方には、
Right! And for those who purchase this set,
笑顔のトワの箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます。
you'll get a Polaroid-style bromide card of a smiling Towa with a foil-stamped replica signature.
はい！そしてですね、数量限定で直筆サイン入り、
こっちは直筆サインで、お渡ししたいなと思っておりますので、
Yes! And in limited quantities, I'd like to provide them
with actual hand-signed signatures,
ぜひ、どっちも手に入れてくれればなー、と思います。
so I hope you'll try to get your hands on either one.
かわいい！
So cute!
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you very much.
ということで、以上、こんな感じで、常闇トワ6周年記念のグッズの紹介でしたー！
And with that, that was the introduction of the Tokoyami Towa 6th Anniversary goods!
シルべと、常闇トワのグッズ、両方よろしくお願いいたします！
Please check out both the Shirube and Tokoyami Towa goods!
ということで、今日は見てくれてありがとう！
Anyway, thanks for watching today!
この後はメン限でライブしますから、ぜひよろしくお願いいたします。
I'll be doing a members-only live stream after this, so please look forward to it.
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃあね、メンバーシップ加入と、グッズ購入と、全部よろしくね！
See ya! Please join the membership and buy the goods—all of it!
あけおめー！バイバイ！
Happy New Year! Bye-bye!